export default function() {
	return [
		{
			answer: "Joel",
			question: "Character's first name that Tom Cruise played in Risky Business?",
			option_1: "Eric",
			option_2: "Joel",
			option_3: "Tommy",
			option_4: "Steven",
			id: "1"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Brittany Murphy",
			question: "This actress starred opposite Ashton Kutcher in the movie Just Married?",
			option_1: "Kate Hudson",
			option_2: "Cameron Diaz",
			option_3: "Mila Kunis",
			option_4: "Brittany Murphy",
			id: "2"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Ian McKellen",
			question: "This actor played Magneto in the movie XMEN?",
			option_1: "Ian McKellen",
			option_2: "Christopher Lee",
			option_3: "Patrick Stewart",
			option_4: "Anthony Hopkins",
			id: "3"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Iceman",
			question: "Val Kilmer's character name in Top Gun?",
			option_1: "Maverick",
			option_2: "Viper",
			option_3: "Goose",
			option_4: "Iceman",
			id: "4"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Biochemist",
			question: "Nicolas Cage's character has this profession in the movie The Rock?",
			option_1: "Biochemist",
			option_2: "Police Officer",
			option_3: "Paramedic",
			option_4: "Taxi Driver",
			id: "5"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Christian Bale",
			question: "This actor was the lead in the 1992 musical Newsies?",
			option_1: "Heath Ledger",
			option_2: "Christian Bale",
			option_3: "Leonardo DiCaprio",
			option_4: "Tom Cruise",
			id: "6"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Natalie Portman",
			question: "This actress played Queen Amidala in Star Wars Episodes I-III?",
			option_1: "Keira Knightley",
			option_2: "Mila Kunis",
			option_3: "Natalie Portman",
			option_4: "Anne Hathaway",
			id: "7"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Code Red",
			question: "Col. Nathan R. Jessup ordered this in A Few Good Men?",
			option_1: "Pizza",
			option_2: "Code Red",
			option_3: "Nuclear Launch",
			option_4: "Bannana Split",
			id: "8"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Pedro",
			question: "Who is Napolean Dynamite's best friend?",
			option_1: "Jorge",
			option_2: "Paco",
			option_3: "Pedro",
			option_4: "Ricky",
			id: "9"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "James Earl Jones",
			question: "The voice behind Darth Vader?",
			option_1: "James Earl Jones",
			option_2: "Peter Cullen",
			option_3: "Jeremy Irons",
			option_4: "Morgan Freeman",
			id: "10"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Jeremy Irons",
			question: "The voice behind Scar from The Lion King?",
			option_1: "James Earl Jones",
			option_2: "Peter Cullen",
			option_3: "Jeremy Irons",
			option_4: "Morgan Freeman",
			id: "11"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Peter Cullen",
			question: "The voice behind Optimus Prime in Transformers?",
			option_1: "James Earl Jones",
			option_2: "Peter Cullen",
			option_3: "Jeremy Irons",
			option_4: "Leonard Nimoy",
			id: "12"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Hans",
			question: "The villain that Alan Rickman portrays in the original Die Hard?",
			option_1: "Albert",
			option_2: "Ivan",
			option_3: "Satan",
			option_4: "Hans",
			id: "13"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Iowa",
			question: "Field of Dreams takes place on a corn field in?",
			option_1: "Kansas",
			option_2: "Iowa",
			option_3: "Nebraska",
			option_4: "Ohio",
			id: "14"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Liv Tyler",
			question: "This actress plays Bruce Willis's daughter in Armageddon?",
			option_1: "Liv Tyler",
			option_2: "Alicia Siverstone",
			option_3: "Cameron Diaz",
			option_4: "Tea Leoni",
			id: "15"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Los Angeles",
			question: "In what city is the Nakatomi Plaza in the original Die Hard?",
			option_1: "New York",
			option_2: "Chicago",
			option_3: "Los Angeles",
			option_4: "San Francisco",
			id: "16"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "President",
			question: "What is Morgan Freeman's character in Deep Impact?",
			option_1: "Scientist",
			option_2: "Detective",
			option_3: "President",
			option_4: "Professor",
	    	id: "17"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Doctor",
			question: "What is Harrison Ford's character in The Fugitive?",
			option_1: "Scientist",
			option_2: "Doctor",
			option_3: "President",
			option_4: "Archaeologist",
			id: "18"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "50 mph",
			question: "In Speed Keanu Reeves must keep the bus above what speed?",
			option_1: "45 mph",
			option_2: "50 mph",
			option_3: "55 mph",
			option_4: "60 mph",
			id: "19"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Dennis Hopper",
			question: "This actor plays the villan in the movie Speed?",
			option_1: "Dennis Hopper",
			option_2: "Alan Rickman",
			option_3: "Joe Pesci",
			option_4: "Ray Liotta",
			id: "20"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Robert De Niro",
			question: "This actor plays the iconic mobster James Conway in Goodfellas?",
			option_1: "Al Pacino",
			option_2: "Ray Liotta",
			option_3: "Joe Pesci",
			option_4: "Robert De Niro",
			id: "21"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Liam Neeson",
			question: "The voice of Good Cop/Bad Cop in The Lego Movie?",
			option_1: "Will Ferrell",
			option_2: "Liam Neeson",
			option_3: "Will Arnett",
			option_4: "Chris Pratt",
			id: "22"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "The Lego Movie",
			question: "If you've heard the song 'Everything is Awesome', then you've seen this movie?",
			option_1: "Wreck-It Ralph",
			option_2: "Big Hero 6",
			option_3: "Despicable Me",
			option_4: "The Lego Movie",
			id: "23"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Vector",
			question: "Jason Segal voices this villain in Despicable Me?",
			option_1: "Vector",
			option_2: "Dr. Nefario",
			option_3: "Mr. Perkins",
			option_4: "Paul",
			id: "24"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Julie Andrews",
			question: "This actress played Mary Poppins?",
			option_1: "Audrey Hepburn",
			option_2: "Julie Andrews",
			option_3: "Carol Burnett",
			option_4: "Glynis Johns",
			id: "25"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Marlon Brando",
			question: "This actor played Don Vito Corleone in the original Godfather in 1972?",
			option_1: "Al Pacino",
			option_2: "James Caan",
			option_3: "Marlon Brando",
			option_4: "Robert De Niro",
			id: "26"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Robert Duvall",
			question: "Secondhand Lions stared 2 old men, Michael Caine and ?",
			option_1: "Walter Matthau",
			option_2: "Jack Lemmon",
			option_3: "James Garner",
			option_4: "Robert Duvall",
			id: "27"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "12 Monkeys",
			question: "Bruce Willis played a time traveling criminal in what movie?",
			option_1: "Timecop",
			option_2: "Die Hard",
			option_3: "Fifth Element",
			option_4: "12 Monkeys",
			id: "28"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "feet",
			question: "Charlie Chaplin insured which part of his body?",
			option_1: "hands",
			option_2: "feet",
			option_3: "mustache",
			option_4: "knees",
			id: "29"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "oscars",
			question: "What did Maron Brando and George C Scott both refuse?",
			option_1: "room service",
			option_2: "stunt doubles",
			option_3: "money",
			option_4: "oscars",
			id: "30"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "James Bond",
			question: "What famous role did both Cary Grant and Noel Coward reject?",
			option_1: "James Bond",
			option_2: "The Godfather",
			option_3: "Dirty Harry",
			option_4: "Atticus Finch",
			id: "31"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Risky Business",
			question: "What was Tom Cruise's 1st box office film?",
			option_1: "Top Gun",
			option_2: "The Outsiders",
			option_3: "Risky Business",
			option_4: "All the Right Moves",
			id: "32"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Reservoir Dogs",
			question: "Quentin Tarantino had his directorial debut with what film?",
			option_1: "Reservoir Dogs",
			option_2: "Pulp Fiction",
			option_3: "Desparado",
			option_4: "Jackie Brown",
			id: "33"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Henry",
			question: "What is Indiana Jones first name?",
			option_1: "Paul",
			option_2: "Christopher",
			option_3: "George",
			option_4: "Henry",
			id: "34"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "John Carpenter",
			question: "Who directed the Halloween series of films?",
			option_1: "Wes Craven",
			option_2: "John Carpenter",
			option_3: "Alfred Hitchcock",
			option_4: "Tobe Hooper",
			id: "35"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Wes Craven",
			question: "Who directed the Nighmare on Elm Street series of films?",
			option_1: "Wes Craven",
			option_2: "John Carpenter",
			option_3: "Alfred Hitchcock",
			option_4: "Tobe Hooper",
			id: "36"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Wes Craven",
			question: "Who directed the Nighmare on Elm Street series of films?",
			option_1: "Wes Craven",
			option_2: "John Carpenter",
			option_3: "Alfred Hitchcock",
			option_4: "Tobe Hooper",
			id: "37"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "8",
			question: "How many total films are there in the Nighmare on Elm Street series?",
			option_1: "5",
			option_2: "6",
			option_3: "7",
			option_4: "8",
			id: "38"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Uncle Rico",
			question: "Napolean Dynamite's uncle was played by Jon Gries with the character name of?",
			option_1: "Uncle Jorge",
			option_2: "Uncle Pedro",
			option_3: "Uncle Rico",
			option_4: "Uncle John",
			id: "39"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Dirty Harry Callahan",
			question: "Frank Sinatra, John Wayne, and Paul Newman all rejected which role?",
			option_1: "The Godfather",
			option_2: "Dirty Harry Callahan",
			option_3: "James Bond",
			option_4: "Santa Claus",
			id: "40"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Enter the Dragon",
			question: "What was Bruce Lee's first Hollywood produced film?",
			option_1: "Enter the Dragon",
			option_2: "The Big Boss",
			option_3: "The Chinese Connection",
			option_4: "The Way of the Dragon",
			id: "41"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "The Way of the Dragon",
			question: "In what Bruce Lee film did he square off against Chuck Norris?",
			option_1: "Enter the Dragon",
			option_2: "The Big Boss",
			option_3: "The Chinese Connection",
			option_4: "The Way of the Dragon",
			id: "42"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Game of Death",
			question: "Bruce Lee never finished this film, which was to feature Kareem Abdul-Jabbar?",
			option_1: "Enter the Dragon",
			option_2: "The Big Boss",
			option_3: "Game of Death",
			option_4: "The Way of the Dragon",
			id: "43"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Bill Murray",
			question: "This actor played Dr. Peter Venkman in the original Ghostbusters?",
			option_1: "Dan Aykroyd",
			option_2: "Harold Ramis",
			option_3: "Bill Murray",
			option_4: "Rick Moranis",
			id: "44"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Harold Ramis",
			question: "This actor played Dr. Egon Spengler in the original Ghostbusters?",
			option_1: "Dan Aykroyd",
			option_2: "Harold Ramis",
			option_3: "Bill Murray",
			option_4: "Rick Moranis",
			id: "45"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Ethan Hunt",
			question: "Tom Cruise's character name in the Mission Impossible film series?",
			option_1: "Cole Trickle",
			option_2: "Roy Miller",
			option_3: "Jack Reacher",
			option_4: "Ethan Hunt",
			id: "46"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Michael Keaton",
			question: "This actor played Batman in Tim Burton's 1989 Batman?",
			option_1: "Christian Bale",
			option_2: "Michael Keaton",
			option_3: "Adam West",
			option_4: "Val Kilmer",
			id: "47"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Gina",
			question: "Tony Montana has a sister in the movie Scarface with this name?",
			option_1: "Maria",
			option_2: "Christina",
			option_3: "Gina",
			option_4: "Sarah",
			id: "48"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Scarface",
			question: "Al Pacino plays the role of Tony Montana in this film?",
			option_1: "Scarface",
			option_2: "The Godfather",
			option_3: "Taxi Driver",
			option_4: "Heat",
			id: "49"
	  	},
	  	{
			answer: "Lefty",
			question: "In Donnie Brasco, Johnny Depp's character befriends Al Pacino's character named?",
			option_1: "Scarface",
			option_2: "Lefty",
			option_3: "Tony Montana",
			option_4: "Sonny",
			id: "50"
	  	}
	];
}
